<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Visit Sommières</string>
    <string name="intro_text">Sommières is a beautiful historic town with ancient origins, situated in the valley of
        the Vidourle river half way between Montpellier and Nimes, and surrounded by the vineyards of the
        Gard, department of Languedoc-Roussillon. Throughout its history, Sommières has remained a thriving industrial
        city, working on textiles (a cloth formerly known as Sommières) and famous for its aromatic essences.
    So sit back and relax while we show you around some of the best features of Sommières. We have also linked to a blog
    below and some videos uploaded to YouTube.</string>
    <string name="video_tour">90 second photo tour</string>
    <string name="aerial">Aerial drone tour of Sommières</string>
    <string name="hostel">A tour of Sommières\' hostel</string>

    <!-- Visit Fragment-->
    <string name="visit_gps1">geo:37.7749,-122.4194</string>
    <string name="visit_nameOfAtt1">The Roman Bridge</string>
    <string name="visit_shortDes1">The most important historic monument in Sommieres is the bridge across the river,
                    dating from the 1st century</string>
    <string name="visit_moreIn1">blah blah blah</string>

    <string name="visit_gps2">blah2</string>
    <string name="visit_nameOfAtt2">Chateau Villevieille</string>
    <string name="visit_shortDes2">The town and its magnificent castle overlook the Vidourle river plain.
        The castle tower dates back to the 10th century whereas the main part of the castle was renovated
        in the Renaissance style at the end of the 16th century.</string>
    <string name="visit_moreIn2">blah blah blah</string>

    <string name="visit_gps3">blah3</string>
    <string name="visit_nameOfAtt3">Jazz à Junas</string>
    <string name="visit_shortDes3">25th edition. Faithful to its commitments Jazz in Junas goes always and
        again to meet all audiences to give pleasure and discover jazz in all its forms.</string>
    <string name="visit_moreIn3">blah</string>

    <string name="visit_gps4">blah4</string>
    <string name="visit_nameOfAtt4">The Green Trail</string>
    <string name="visit_shortDes4">From Sommières to Caveirac, in the outskirts of  Nîmes, the green trail allows
        for an outdoor excursion in pleasant and safe conditions.</string>
    <string name="visit_moreIn4">blah</string>

    <string name="visit_gps5">blah5</string>
    <string name="visit_nameOfAtt5">Le Roc de Massereau</string>
    <string name="visit_shortDes5">Welcome to the Roc de Massereau, the adventure park of
        Sommières Montpellier et Nîmes.</string>
    <string name="visit_moreIn5">blah</string>

    <!-- Eat Fragment-->









</resources>
